Southwest Folklore Center Sound Disc Collection, 1945-1987
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Sioux City Sue -- My little girl, Ramsey, Clay and the Old Timers, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc (7 min.), analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Clay Ramsey and the Old Timers... Harry Raby, pianist... Singing square dance without calls... Sioux City Sue -- My little girl --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8042 (10in.)
- Shenandoah waltz -- On top of Old Smokey, Martin, Jay, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Organ music by Jay Martin... Shenandoah waltz -- On top of Old Smokey --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8048 (10in.)
- Virginia reel -- Brown eyed Mary, Ramsey, Clay and the Old Timers, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Clay Ramsey and the Old Timers... Johnny Melton and Mrs. Johnny Melton, callers... Square dance with calls... Virginia reel/Irish washerwoman -- Brown eyed Mary --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8051 (10in.)
- Steel guitar rag -- Cindy, Cal Golden's Arkansas Mountain Boys, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc (7 min.), analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Cal Golden's Arkansas Mountain Boys... Harry Raby, pianist... Square dance without calls... Steel guitar rag -- Cindy --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8053 (10in.)
- Sweet Georgia Brown -- When you wore a tulip, Cal Golden's Arkansas Mountain Boys, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc (8 min.), analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Cal Golden's Arkansas Mountain Boys... Harry Raby, pianist... Square dance without calls... Sweet Georgia Brown -- When you wore a tulip --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8054 (10in.)
- Split the ring -- Farmer's daughter, Johnny Balmer's Grand Canyon Cabin Boys, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Johnny Balmer's Grand Canyon Cabin Boys... Ed Bossing, caller... Square dance with calls... Split the ring/Ragtime Annie -- Farmer's daughter/Soldiers joy --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8058 (10in.)
- Oklahoma cyclone -- Chain lightening, Delk, Fiddlin' Forrest and his Gully Jumpers, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc (7 min.), analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Fiddlin' Forrest Delk and his Gully Jumpers... Butch Nelson, caller... Square dance with calls and square dance without calls... Oklahoma cyclone -- Chain lightening --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8061 (10in.)
- Too old to cut the mustard, Cal Golden's Arkansas Mountain Boys, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc (7 min.), analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Cal Golden's Arkansas Mountain Boys... Cal Golden, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance without calls... Too old to cut the mustard --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8066 (10in.)
- Barnacle Bill square, The Arkansas Mountain Boys, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by The Arkansas Mountain Boys... Cal Golden, caller... Singing square dance with calls... Barnacle Bill square --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8067 (10in.)
- Texas plains, Cal Golden's Arkansas Mountain Boys, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Cal Golden's Arkansas Mountain Boys... Cal Golden, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance without calls... Texas plains --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8069 (10in.)
- Inside out outside in -- Yucaipa twister, Ramsey, Clay and the Old Timers, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc (9 min.), analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Clay Ramsey and the Old Timers... Johnny Melton, caller... Square dance with calls... Inside out outside in -- Yucaipa twister --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8074 (10in.)
- Delk's Berlin polka -- Delk's schottiche, Delk, Fiddlin' Forrest and his Gully Jumpers, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Fiddlin' Forrest Delk and his Gully Jumpers... Delk's Berlin polka -- Delk's schottiche --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8076 (10in.)
- Don't look back -- Apache square, Ramsey, Clay and the Old Timers, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc (8 min.), analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Clay Ramsey and the Old Timers... Jim Brook, caller... Square dance with calls... Don't look back (Music: Chinese breakdown) -- Apache square (Music: Flop eared mule) --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8083 (10in.)
- Hometown square, Johnny Balmer's Grand Canyon Boys, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Johnny Balmer's Grand Canyon Boys... Johnny Schultz, caller... Square dance with calls and square dance without calls... Hometown square --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8085 (10in.)
- Cow counties hoedown -- Rangers hoedown, Cal Golden's Arkansas Mountain Boys, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc (7 min.), analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Cal Golden's Arkansas Mountain Boys... Square dance without calls... Cow counties hoedown -- Rangers hoedown --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8088 (10in.)
- Forty years ago -- Justrite schottiche, Cal Golden's Arkansas Mountain Boys, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc (7 min.), analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Roy Sexton and his Arizona Hoedowners... Roy Sexton, fiddle; Bill Harris, guitar; Clyde Armentrout, bass; Johnny Balmer, banjo... Forty years ago -- Justrite schottiche --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8091 (10in.)
- Sleep -- La Golondrina, Martin, Jay, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Jay Martin at the Hammond organ with guitar and bass... Recorded under supervision of Joe Boykin... Sleep -- La Golondrina --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8092 (10in.)
- I miss my Swiss -- Kiss waltz, Jerry Jacka Trio, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Jerry Jacka Trio... Couple or mixer dance... I miss my Swiss (My swiss miss misses me) -- Kiss waltz/Kiss me again --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8101 (10in.)
- Mister Sandman, Jerry Jacka Trio, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Jerry Jacka Trio... Johnny Schultz, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance without calls... Mister Sandman --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8104 (10in.)
- Split your corners hash -- Blue Island blister, Johnny Balmer's Grand Canyon Boys, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Johnny Balmer's Grand Canyon Boys... Roy Sutton, caller... Square dance with calls... Split your corners hash/Tom and Jerry -- Blue Island blister/Fireball special --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8105 (10in.)
- The Route --Oak Lawn merrygoround, Johnny Balmer's Grand Canyon Boys, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Johnny Balmer's Grand Canyon Boys... "Uncle Walt" Wentworth, caller... Square dance with calls... The Route/Fireball special --Oak Lawn merrygoround/Tom and Jerry --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8106 (10in.)
- Walkabout -- Joyride, Jerry Jacka Trio, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Jerry Jacka Trio... Round dance... Walkabout/Walkin' along) -- Joyride --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8107 (10in.)
- Teasin', The Cottonpickin' Five, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by The Cottonpickin' Five... Butch Nelson, caller... Chuck Moon, fiddle; Johnny Balmer, banjo; Jerry Jacka, accordion; Bill Harris, guitar; Everett Helman, bass... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance without calls... Teasin' --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8109 (10in.)
- Sailing down that old green river, The Cottonpickin' Five, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by The Cottonpickin' Five... Butch Nelson, caller... Chuck Moon, fiddle; Johnny Balmer, banjo; Jerry Jacka, accordion; Bill Harris, guitar; Everett Helman, bass... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance without calls... Sailing down that old green river --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8110 (10in.)
- Sailing down that old green river, The Cottonpickin' Five, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by The Cottonpickin' Five... Butch Nelson, caller... Chuck Moon, fiddle; Johnny Balmer, banjo; Jerry Jacka, accordion; Bill Harris, guitar; Everett Helman, bass... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance without calls... Sailing down that old green river --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8110 (10in.)
- Hoop dee doo, The Cottonpickin' Five, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by The Cottonpickin' Five... Butch Nelson, caller... Chuck Moon, fiddle; Johnny Balmer, banjo; Jerry Jacka, accordion; Bill Harris, guitar; Everett Helman, bass... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance without calls... Hoop dee doo --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8111 (10in.)
- Raggin' the call, The Cottonpickin' Five, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by The Cottonpickin' Five... Butch Nelson, caller... Chuck Moon, fiddle; Johnny Balmer, banjo; Jerry Jacka, accordion; Bill Harris, guitar; Everett Helman, bass... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance without calls... Raggin' the call --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8112 (10in.)
- Truck stop -- Silver bells, Jerry Jacka Trio, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Jerry Jacka Trio... Singing square dance without calls... Truck stop -- Silver bells --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8114 (10in.)
- Lookin' back, Jerry Jacka Trio, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Jerry Jacka Trio... Johnny Schultz, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance without calls... Lookin' back --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8119 (10in.)
- Dreamland tonight -- Skin-'em rinky dee, Barr, Dick, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Dick Barr at the organ... Round dance... Dreamland tonight -- Skin-'em rinky dee --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8120 (10in.)
- Loose talk, Jerry Jacka Trio, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Jerry Jacka Trio... Johnny Schultz, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance without calls... Loose talk --; SWF 1980.1D(78).8121 (10in.)
- Step right up and say howdy, Jerry Jacka and the Boys, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Jerry Jacka and the Boys... Johnny Schultz, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance without calls... Step right up and say howdy --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8123 (10in.)
- Poor boy, Jerry Jacka Trio, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Jerry Jacka Trio... Johnny Schultz, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance without calls... Poor boy --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8124A (10in.)
- Poor boy, Jerry Jacka Trio, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Jerry Jacka Trio... Johnny Schultz, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance without calls... Poor boy --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8124B (10in.)
- Dream on, Jerry Jacka Trio, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Jerry Jacka Trio... Johnny Schultz, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance without calls... Dream on --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8126 (10in.)
- New lady of Spain, Jerry Jacka Trio, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Jerry Jacka Trio... Johnny Schultz, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance without calls... New lady of Spain --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8128 (10in.)
- Tulsa square, Burton's Wranglers, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Burton's Wranglers... Max Engle, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance without calls... Tulsa square --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8129 (10in.)
- Square 'em through -- Hashin' the bends, Johnny Balmer's Grand Canyon Boys, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Johnny Balmer's Grand Canyon Boys... Bill Castner, caller... Square dance with calls... Square 'em through/Fiddler's dream -- Hashin' the bends/Beaver Creek --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8130 (10in.)
- Platter patter -- Warmer upper, Schultz, Johnny, caller, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Calls by Johnny Schultz... Square dance with calls... Platter patter -- Warmer upper --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8132 (10in.)
- Let's face it, Burton's Wranglers, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Burton's Wranglers... Max Engle, caller... Square dance with calls and square dance without calls... Let's face it --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8133 (10in.)
- Arizona star -- Arizona star hash, The Old Timers, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by The Old Timers... Johnny Schultz, caller... Square dance with calls... Arizona star -- Arizona star hash --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8136 (10in.)
- Sally Goodin -- Sally Goodin hash, The Old Timers, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by The Old Timers... Johnny Schultz, caller... Square dance with calls... Sally Goodin -- Sally Goodin hash --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8138 (10in.)
- Split your corner -- Split your corner hash, The Old Timers, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by The Old Timers... Johnny Schultz, caller... Square dance with calls... Split your corner -- Split your corner hash --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8139 (10in.)
- Wham, bam, The Four Squares, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by The Four Squares... Fred Bailey, caller... Square dance with calls and square dance instrumental... Wham, bam --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8147 (10in.)
- Look on the good side, Jerry Jacka Trio, 1950; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Old Timer Record Co., c1950; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Jerry Jacka Trio... Johnny Schultz, caller... Square dance with calls and square dance instrumental... Look on the good side --; SWF 1980.1/D(78).8148 (10in.)
- Bill Bailey -- St. Louis blues, Allen, Jerry (Mr. Banjo), Phoenix, AZ., Dash Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Jerry Allen... Bill Bailey -- St. Louis blues --; SWF 81.3/D(45).2401 (7in.)
- Sweet Jennie Lee, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Bob Johnson, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Sweet Jennie Lee --; SWF 81.3/D(45).2501 (7in.)
- Little Spanish restaurant, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Al Brownlee, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Little Spanish restaurant --; SWF 81.3/D(45).2505; (7in.)
- Weeping willow, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Dale Durbin, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Weeping willow --; SWF 81.3/D(45).2509 (7in.)
- Loudmouth, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Earl Neff, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Loudmouth --; SWF 81.3/D(45).2511 (7in.)
- Whispering Sands, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Virg Knackstedt, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Whispering Sands --; SWF 81.3/D(45).2512 (7in.)
- Old town hall, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Bill Schroeder, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Old town hall --; SWF 81.3/D(45).2513 (7in.)
- Alone with you, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Gentry Harrison, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Alone with you --; SWF 81.3/D(45).2514 (7in.)
- Gate of love, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Bob Graham, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Gate of love (Swing wide your gate of love) --; SWF 81.3/D(45).2515 (7in.)
- Lullaby waltz -- Between you and me, The Dashers, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by The Dashers... Round dance - instrumental... Lullaby waltz -- Between you and me --; SWF 81.3/D(45).2516 (7in.)
- Lullaby waltz -- Between you and me, The Dashers, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by The Dashers... Round dance - instrumental... Lullaby waltz -- Between you and me --; SWF 81.3/D(45).2516 (7in.)
- Square dance honeymoon, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Earl Neff, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Square dance honeymoon/Honeymoon on a rocket ship ---; SWF 81.3/D(45).2517 (7in.)
- Ya gotta be my baby, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Dale Durbin, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Ya gotta be my baby --; SWF 81.3/D(45).2518 (7in.)
- Silver dew, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Bob Johnston, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Silver dew/Silver dew on the blue grass tonight --; SWF 81.3/D(45).2519 (7in.)
- Beautiful Texas, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Dale Durbin, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Beautiful Texas --; SWF 81.3/D(45).2520 (7in.)
- Somebody loves you, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Earl Neff, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Somebody loves you --; SWF 81.3/D(45).2521 (7in.)
- Way out there, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... George Vagtborg, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Way out there --; SWF 81.3/D(45).2522 (7in.)
- I'll be sixteen next Sunday -- Up jumped the Devil --, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Instrumental... I'll be sixteen next Sunday -- Up jumped the Devil --; SWF 81.3/D(45).2524 (7in.)
- Little Lulu, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... "Singin Sam" Mitchell, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Little Lulu --; SWF 81.3/D(45).2525 (7in.)
- There's nothing as sweet as my baby, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Johnnie Roth, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... There's nothing as sweet as my baby --; SWF 81.3/D(45).2526 (7in.)
- Bully of the town, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Larry Garrett, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Bully of the town --; SWF 81.3/D(45).2527 (7in.)
- Hey, good lookin', Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Dale Durbin, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Hey, good lookin' --; SWF 81.3/D(45).2528 (7in.)
- Way down south, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Del Price, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Way down south --; SWF 81.3/D.(45).2529 (7in.)
- Shine, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Bob Johnston, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Shine --; SWF 81.3/D.(45).2530 (7in.)
- Swingin' man, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Chuck Raley, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Swingin' man --; SWF 81.3/D.(45).2531 (7in.)
- North, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Jack Ikler, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... North --; SWF 81.3/D.(45).2532 (7in.)
- Dime a dozen, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Gaylord Tannat, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Dime a dozen --; SWF 81.3/D.(45).2533 (7in.)